<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- 
	1. Order events by date.
	2. Expired events will be listed in past events.
	3. Beware special characters! (<, >, &, etc) Enclose them in <![CDATA[  ]]> or replace with HTML entities.
-->
<events>

<event>
	<expire>20150530</expire>
	<date>May 30, 3-7pm</date>
	<location>B240</location>
	<title>Beginner's Programming Competition Spring 2015</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Taking only undergrad courses? Love programming? Love ninjas? This is the event you've been waiting for! 
	We like to have a little fun here and there, and now we want to share that joy and happiness with you through a ninja-themed BPC! 
	Come out and spend a mischievous day with us at the Ninja Academy for this Spring's Beginner's Programming Competition, sponsored 
	by Facebook!! <a href="competition.html">Register here</a>.</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150525</expire>
	<date>May 25, 6pm</date>
	<location>B225</location>
	<title>Beginner's Programming Competition Spring 2015: Ninja Training Session</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>For those of you who are new to BPC or who just want more problem solving experience, come out to our Ninja 
	Training Session! </p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150518</expire>
	<date>May 18</date>
	<location>TBD</location>
	<title>Year End Banquet</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>As the year winds to an end, WIC will be holding its annual year end banquet to 
	celebrate the past year, send off our seniors, and introduce the new officer board. It will be an evening of food and fun 
	you won't want to miss!</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150515</expire>
	<date>May 15, 4-5pm</date>
	<location>Jacobs 4309</location>
	<title>Spring GBM #2</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Come join us for our last GBM of the year!</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150430</expire>
	<date>April 30</date>
	<location>Jacobs 4309</location>
	<title>Faculty Coffee Hour</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Ever want to talk to your professors outside of class but not sure how? Get a chance to network with some 
	great CS professors over free coffee and snacks provided by WIC. Our Faculty Coffee Hour will feature professors such as 
	Christine Alvarado, Jeanne Ferrante, Rick Ord, and Leo Porter!</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150409</expire>
	<date>Thurs Apr 9, 6:30pm </date>
	<location>CSE 1202</location>
	<title>Facebook + UCSD WIC Panel</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Please join Facebook + WICS at UCSD for an exciting conversation around women in technology 
		and to hear first-hand what it is like to work in different areas of engineering at Facebook. 
		Brina Lee (UCSD alum, Software Engineer on Instagram), Yuzhi Zheng (to discuss web development and open source technology), 
		and Prashasti Baid (Production Engineer) will join us to talk about what they do at FB and how they got there!</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150407</expire>
	<date>Tue Apr 7, 4pm</date>
	<location>EBU1- Henry Booker Room</location>
	<title>Spring GBM #1</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Join WIC for our first spring GBM to hear about more exciting events and opportunities we have planned for you this quarter! 
	We'll also be going over some tips for the upcoming job fair, this year's Grace Hopper Celebration of Women in Computing, and officer applications 
	for next year. If you're considering applying, this'll be a great opportunity for you to meet the current officers if you haven't already!</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150404</expire>
	<date>Sat Apr 4</date>
	<location>Town Square</location>
	<title>Tabling on Triton Day</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Volunteer to help out the WIC table for prospective students! </p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150402</expire>
	<date>Thurs Apr 2, 7pm</date>
	<location>CSE 1202</location>
	<title>Alumni Startup Panel</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Come out and listen to UCSD alumni give their stories and advice about creating a startup. </p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150307</expire>
	<date>Sat Mar 7</date>
	<location>TBD</location>
	<title>WI 15 Beginner Programming Competition</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p><a href="competition.html">Register here</a>.</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150228</expire>
	<date>Week 8 TBD</date>
	<location>TBD</location>
	<title>Mock Interview Night</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Worried about landing the interview you got after the career fair? Come out to WIC's Mock Interview Night and practice some technical interview problems commonly asked by companies! You'll get the opportunity to receive feedback and tips from students who have successfully interviewed with companies in the past.
	If you'd like, you can also help out your fellow students and be an interviewer! </p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150220</expire>
	<date>Fri Feb 20</date>
	<location>PC Ballrooms East and West</location>
	<title>DECaF</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Disciplines of Engineering Career Fair (DECaF), established in 1998, is the only annual student-managed multidisciplinary career fair at the University of California, San Diego. This event provides company representatives a unique opportunity to interact and engage with UCSD's talented engineering students regarding career options, internships, and permanent or summer employment opportunities. </p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150207</expire>
	<date>Sat Feb 7</date>
	<location>CSE B225</location>
	<title>Mentor-Mentee Social</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>To kick-off the Mentorship Program WIC will have a Mentor/Mentee Social this Saturday in B225. Come and meet your mentor/mentee and make your own yogurt parfait!! We will also be providing more information on how you can make your mentor/mentee experience the best that it can be. 
	</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150122</expire>
	<date>Thurs Jan 22</date>
	<location>Henry Booker Room</location>
	<title>WIC Winter GBM #1</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>WIC's first GBM of Winter quarter is this Friday! Our theme this time is Careers in CS. We'll be discussing career options in CS for you to keep in mind during DECaF, the upcoming engineering career fair. See you there!</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20150117</expire>
	<date>Fri Jan 16- Sat Jan 17</date>
	<location>Qualcomm Conference Center (Jacobs Hall)</location>
	<title>Hack Night II</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Join WIC and TESC for Hack Night, 8pm-8am in the Qualcomm Conference Center (Jacobs Hall)! This is the perfect chance to test out your hacking skills or start that long-term project you've always wanted to, since we’ll be providing online resources that'll explain how to set up a website, apps, servers, and Github. You can also work on a personal project you’ve already started. We'll have mentors available to help you out. </p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

</events>