<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- 
	1. Order events by date.
	2. Expired events will be listed in past events.
	3. Beware special characters! (<, >, &, etc) Enclose them in <![CDATA[  ]]> or replace with HTML entities.
-->
<events>


<event>
	<expire>20140524</expire>
	<date>Sat May 24, 3-7:30PM</date>
	<location>CSE B230</location>
	<title>Beginner's Programming Competition (Spring '14)</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p><a href="competition.html">Register here</a>.</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>


<event>
	<expire>20140522</expire>
	<date>Thurs May 22, 7pm - 9pm</date>
	<location>Village West Tower (Building 1) on the 15th Floor</location>
	<title>End of the Year Banquet</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p>Come celebrate the end of a great year with WIC with an opening keynote from Lalitta Ghandikota (Informatica) about personal branding, honoring for our graduating seniors and officers, and meeting our new board for 2014-2015. It will be a semi-formal event, so please come dressed nicely! Dinner will be provided.</p> ]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20140424</expire>
	<date>Thurs Apr 24, 6:30pm</date>
	<location>CSE 1202</location>
	<title>Talk and Q&amp;A with Elena Silenok</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p>Eve and WIC are excited to co-host an alumni tech talk with Elena Silenok, founder of Clothia, and a former UCSD master's student with an MS in Systems and Networking concentration, Network Security focus!</p>

<p>Elena Silenok, founder of Clothia, a fashion destination iPad app, will be joining us this Thursday for a talk about start-ups and the different options after a degree in CS.
After, she will be holding a Q&A session, where you can have the opportunity to ask her any questions about turning an idea into a startup, how having a masters in security has affected her career in the industry, or any other questions you can think of!</p>

<p>Come join us this Thursday for a talk about startups, different options after a degree in CS, and a Q&A session that will be sure not to disappoint!
</p> ]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20140416</expire>
	<date>Wed Apr 16, 1:30pm</date>
	<location>Jacobs Hall 4th Floor, Room 4309</location>
	<title>Faculty Coffee hour</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p>Get a chance to network with some great CS professors over coffee provided by WIC. Talk about classes, ask for industry advice, or just have a quick chat over a cup of joe. Professors that will be attending include Rick Ord, Christine Alvarado, YY Zhou, and Philip Papadopoulos!</p> ]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20140410</expire>
	<date>Thu Apr 10, 5pm</date>
	<location>3rd Floor of the CSE Building</location>
	<title>Spring Mock Interview Night</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p> Still looking for an internship? Nervous for the technical interview? WIC has you covered! Come practice your technical interview skills at our mock interview night! We'll be whiteboard coding with some common questions lots of companies ask. It's a great opportunity to prep for your next technical interview...or just to keep you on your toes! Summer's coming quickly, make sure you're ready to land the interview!</p> ]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20140405</expire>
	<date>Apr 5-6</date>
	<location>Carlsbad</location>
	<title>WIC Goes to CWIC</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p> The Celebration of Women in Computing in Southern California (CWIC-SoCal) conference will be held in northern San Diego County at the Carlsbad by the Sea Resort. It brings together women interested in computer science and information technology to network, share their experiences, learn from each other and, of course, to have fun.</p> ]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20140301</expire>
	<date>Sat Mar 1, 3-7:30PM</date>
	<location>CSE B230</location>
	<title>Beginner's Programming Competition (Winter '14)</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p><a href="competition.html">Register here</a>.</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20140212</expire>
	<date>Wed Feb 12, 7pm-9pm</date>
	<location>3rd Floor of the CSE Building</location>
	<title>Mock Interview Night #2 - with Alumni!</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p>Ever wanted to have a practice interview with an actual engineer at a tech company? WIC is an offering a great opportunity to get mock technical interview prep from UCSD alums who now work in industry! If you had a great experience at our last mock interview prep night, this night should be a bit more official with real software engineers in industry! Learn how to ace the behavorial and technical from the people who hire!</p>
<p><b>Important:</b>
Please sign up to either be interviewed/ or be an interviewer with <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1UqO9Tcwn2iTnVLuPTM3NIjtsB077dipJyC-gbFOHPUA/viewform" target="_blank">this Google doc</a>.</p> ]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>



<event>
	<expire>20140211</expire>
	<date>Wed Feb 11, 5pm-6:30pm</date>
	<location>Henry Booker Room (Room 2512), Jacobs Hall</location>
	<title>Q&amp;A Session with GradWIC</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p>Interested in grad school? Come to our Q&A info session! A panel of grad students will be talking about scholarships, and grad applications! The session will be mainly Q&A style so come with questions and excited to learn how grad school could be a possible path for you! :)</p> ]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20140205</expire>
	<date>Wed Feb 5, 7pm-9pm</date>
	<location>3rd Floor of the CSE Building</location>
	<title>Mock Interview Night</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p>Come hone your technical interview skills with WIC at our mock interview night! We'll be whiteboard coding with some common questions companies ask, and with DECaF less than three weeks away it's a great opportunity to get some practice in. If you already have an internship, we'd love to get your experience with the interview process and feel free to sign up as an interviewer!</p>
<p><b>Important:</b>
Please sign up to either be interviewed/ or be an interviewer with <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1UqO9Tcwn2iTnVLuPTM3NIjtsB077dipJyC-gbFOHPUA/viewform" target="_blank">this Google doc</a>.</p> ]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>


<event>
	<expire>20131123</expire>
	<date>Sat Nov 23, 3PM-7:30PM</date>
	<location>CSE B230 and B240</location>
	<title>Beginner's Programming Competition</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p>The Beginner's Programming Competition is designed specifically with undergrads who have not taken any upper division courses in mind. So if you love to code and want to participate in a programming competition this is a great opportunity for you! <a href="/competition.html">Sign up here</a></p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>


<event>
	<expire>20131113</expire>
	<date>Wed Nov 13, 7PM-9PM</date>
	<location>CSE Building, Third Floor by the elevators</location>
	<title>Interview Prep Night</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p>Brush up on those technical interviewing skills. You'll have the option to choose what topic (i.e. data structures, puzzles) and the way you want the interview conducted (white board, Google docs, paper). It'll be casual so don't stress!</p> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/477454699035530/?ref=4">Facebook link</a></p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20131021</expire>
	<date>Mon Oct 21, 8PM-9:30PM</date>
	<location>WLH 2207</location>
	<title>"Girl Rising" Screening</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p>"If you stop me, there will be other girls who rise up and take my place. I am change."</p>
<p>Directed by Academy Award-nominated director Richard E. Robbins, the film is about the power of education to CHANGE a GIRL-- and the WORLD. Join us for a FREE SCREENING of Girl Rising (featuring Anne Hathaway, Salma Hayek, Selena Gomez, Meryl Streep, Alicia Keys, Kerry Washington and more!) AND FREE SNACKS! Check out the trailer <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BJsvklXhYaE" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>

<p><a href="http://10x10act.org/" target="_blank">10x10 act</a> | <a href="http://girlrising.com/" target="_blank">Girl Rising</a></p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>



<event>
	<expire>20131017</expire>
	<date>Mon Oct 14, 7PM-8:30PM</date>
	<location>Jacobs Hall, Henry Booker Room 2512</location>
	<title>Salesforce Tech Talk</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p>Come join WIC and leading cloud provider SALESFORCE for a tech talk on what Salesforce is all about! Dinner will be provided!</p>

<p>Stay after to chat with Salesforce engineers about what it's like to work at a Forbes' ranked 19th best company to work for or ask about the awesome projects they're working on that make Salesforce America's Most Innovate Company!
</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>20131014</expire>
	<date>Mon Oct 14, Noon-2pm</date>
	<location>Qualcomm Room (1st Floor), Jacobs Hall</location>
	<title>Cisco Tech Talk: "Backpack to Briefcase: Working as a Woman in Technology"</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[ <p> Come join Cisco as we invite some of our female engineers to share their stories and lessons-learned while navigating through their careers. There will be plenty of time for open discussion and networking. Lunch will be provided.</p>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>

<event>
	<expire>00000000</expire>
	<date>Weekly</date>
	<location>Cups, by the CSE Building behind the Bear</location>
	<title>WIC Lunches</title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Come see what your fellow WIC 
			members have been up to and give all that 
			studying and hard work a break! (Bring your own lunch or purchase from Cups)
			</p>
			<p>Dates and times (Fall 2013 Quarter):</p>
			<ul>
			<li>Monday, October 14th  @ 12:00pm - 1:00pm</li>
			<li>Thursday, October 24th @ 1:00pm - 2:00pm</li>
			<li>Wednesday, October 30th @ 12:00pm - 1:00pm</li>
			<li>Tuesday, November 5th @ 12:00pm - 1:00pm</li>
			<li>Thursday, November 14th @ 1:00pm - 2:00pm</li>
			<li>Tuesday, November 26th @ 11:00am -12:00pm</li>
			</ul>]]></desc>
	<link></link>
</event>


</events>
		